<news>
	<entry>
		<date>2024-07-24 19:00:00Z</date>
		<title>Server Rules</title>
		<text>
- All Players are allowed [FF2A00]5 LCB[-] (Land Claim Block) Skynet supporter tiers allow for more depending, if we find you placed more than allowed we might delete them all without warning.
- If you can place a claim and it stays, the spot if yours, please keep in mind its polite to not build on top of your neighbors.
- **If you are gone more than 14 days your LCB will expire and area reset, contact admin for more time.**

- Landmines must be kept inside a fence on your property.
- Glitching, cheating, and using exploits are not permitted.
- Please do not Block or Destroy the major highways, the Biker gangs need them:) You may build over them as long as a jeep can pass safely.
- Do not Fight Zombies on Horde Nights at /Market or /donor 

- This is a PvE server so NO PvP of any kind is allowed, loot, kill zombies, and make new friends, if you want death and mayhem this isn't the server for you.
- Keep the chat and Language respectable, PG that also includes In-Game Voice No defamatory, derogative, or racist comments or names!
			
- No Looting Bases Claimed by a Land Claim Block, this includes anything on their property other than airdrops. if it DINGS when punched, its not for you!!
  if we find you guilty of looting a **CLAIMED** base, even if unlocked you will be punished.
- All doors/chests must be locked, have friends? Pin Code everything, you are responsible for your own belongings. 
  the Thief will get caught and punished, but we will NOT replace your items for YOUR carelessness, LOCK YOUR STUFF!

- All Vehicles Are Ride at OWN Risk, we will not replace them if/when they bug out. That includes Theft, please keep them locked. 
  Also FYI teleporting on Vehicles has been known to make them explode, so maybe don't do that.

- Unlocked vehicles (no matter where in game), workstations, storage containers in general on claimed territory are NOT fair game, you will get caught and removed, just don't do it.

- No griefing players, this covers both actions verbal and physical in the game. This also includes retaliation, 2 wrongs DO NOT make a right.
  In general please just don't be jerks, when possible handle issues amongst yourselves in a nice respectable adult way.
		</text>
		<link></link>
	</entry>
</news>
