<news>
	<entry>
		<date>2024-06-24 23:00:00Z</date>
		<title>7 days to die V1.0 Experimental is out!!!</title>
		<text>All 3 our servers updated to 1.0 experimental and ready for playing!
Please remember this is experimental and some things you know and love wont be available, we will continue to fix and update as we go.
No Donors, Forts or Markets will be available at this time.
		</text>
		<link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/251570/view/6941797558605229581</link>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>2024-06-28 16:00:00Z</date>
		<title>First batch of QOL updates and more!</title>
		<text>Today changes:
- Expanded player inventory from 45 to 60 slots.
- Added 45 different dye colors. All dyes can be found in loot or bought from traders, just like vanilla dyes.
- Supporter buffs are back

IMPORTANT information about City Resets:
- Starting today City resets will happen live, that means server will not run a restart for those.
- Server will give a 30 minutes countdown in chat before city resets.
- If you happen to be running a quest when city rest happens it might reset it for you, same way as if you log out during active quest.
- City resets will reset all marked regions to the day 1 state, it should not wipe your vehicles or remove your player death bag.
		</text>
		<link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/251570/view/7160213079727903916</link>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>2024-06-30 09:00:00Z</date>
		<title>Server restart time changes</title>
		<text>Good day Skynet people! To improve server performance we are adding more server restarts during evening and early night time.
Additionally server will now warn about server restarts 30 minutes ahead instead of 15 minutes.
			
New server restart time:
 - 4AM CST
 - 7AM CST
 - 1PM CST
 - 7PM CST
 - 10PM CST
 - 1AM CST
		</text>
		<link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/251570/view/7160213079727903916</link>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<date>2024-07-03 13:00:00Z</date>
		<title>Oooh, Shinies!</title>
		<text>Today we are adding first batch of craftable items previously available only from creative menu, and more.
- Added Skynet Table Saw. It can be crafted in workbench and all custom items we add will be available  to craft there.
- Added ability to craft almost every door you encounter in the world. All custom doors are available in 11 different colors and will have increased hit points (5000-9000).
Note: Since for some reason TFP decided that all their doors should go reinforced with ugly planks by default, to override that all doors when placed will have 4999/5000 HP.
- Added working Wall oven (can be place inside a wall like wall safe) and working Gas Range, all three are available in 3 colors - White, Grey and Black.
- All above listed working appliances do act as campfires and can be crafted in Skynet Table Saw (crafted at workbench) under Miscellaneous/Decor category.
		</text>
		<link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/251570/view/7160213079727903916</link>
	</entry>
</news>
